Finding Aid for Sesquicentennial Office (University of Michigan) records, 1959-1967
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Sesquicentennial Office (University of Michigan) records 1959-1967
University of Michigan. Sesquicentennial Office.
13 linear feet (in 14 boxes)
87298 Bimu E17 1967 2
Central committee and subcommittee minutes; files relating to major ceremonies, the sesquicentennial award, and the participation of the different University schools and units in the celebration; invitations; topical files; photographs; and audio-tapes of the major ceremonies.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The manuscript records (Donor No. 4564 ) were deposited by various University units, 1968-1970. The photographs were deposited by the University of Michigan Press (Donor No. 2546 ), 1975.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research, except for negatives in box 14, which are restricted to staff use only.
Office established to administer and coordinate celebratory events during the University of Michigan's sesquicentennial anniversary year.
The records of the Sesquicentennial Committee include administrative files (mainly correspondence and minutes) documenting the activities of the committee as a whole and subcommittees related to each of the major ceremonies of the sesquicentennial celebration; audiotapes of major ceremonies; and photographs.
Subjects:
University of Michigan--Anniversaries, etc.; University of Michigan. Sesquicentennial Celebration.; University of Michigan. Sesquicentennial Office.
- Central Committee
  - Correspondence 1963-1967 (Box 1)
  - Minutes 1963-1967 (Box 1)
- Subcommittee Files
  - Arranged alphabetically (Box 1)
- Major Ceremony I
  - Correspondence 1963-October 1966 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence November 1966-1967, undated (Box 2)
- Major Ceremony II
  - Correspondence 1964-1967 (Box 2)
  - Speakers' correspondence files
    - Alexandrov (Box 2)
    - Ashby (Box 2)
    - Becker; Boulding (Box 2)
    - Bunting, Capelle; Conant (Box 2)
    - Courvoisier; Foster (Box 2)
    - Gomez; Millas (Box 2)
    - Hannah; Heyns (Box 2)
    - Husain; Kirk; Li Choh-Ming (Box 2)
    - Moeda; Moscoso (Box 2)
    - Murray; Njoku; Pierpont (Box 2)
    - Pusey; Robertson; Rossi-Doria (Box 2)
    - Schoff; Svennilson (Box 2)
    - Wilson; Zurayk (Box 2)
  - Planning Committee Minutes 1964-1966 (Box 2)
- Major Ceremony III
  - Correspondence 1964-1967 (Box 3)
  - Fedele Fauri (chairman) correspondence 1964-1966 (Box 3)
  - Speakers' correspondence (and speech) files
    - Cousins; Dubudge; Erhard (Box 3)
    - Fleming; Gardner; Henry (Box 3)
    - Lasky; Lederle; Litchfield (Box 3)
    - Miller; Norman; Odegaard; Perkins (Box 3)
    - Sepulveda; Stahr (Box 3)
    - Stevens; Webb (Box 3)
    - Fleming, Hafstad; Johnson; Moos (Box 3)
    - Satterthwaite; Shuster; Woodcock; Sutherland; Wright (Box 3)
  - Miscellanea (Box 3)
  - Planning Committee Minutes 1964-1966 (Box 3)
- Major Ceremony IV
  - R.C. Angell correspondence 1963-1967 (Box 3)
  - Speakers' correspondence files
    - Candau; Chandrasekhar (Box 3)
    - Kurylouicz; Myrdal (Box 3)
    - Taylor; Tiselius (Box 3)
    - Urey (Box 3)
  - Publicity 1967 (Box 3)
  - Planning Committee Minutes (Box 3)
- Major Ceremony V
  - Correspondence 1966-1967 (Box 3)
  - Speakers' correspondence files
    - [B-Z] (Box 3)
  - Miscellanea, 2 folders (Box 4)
- Sesquicentennial Award
  - Nominees (Box 4)
  - Nominee Forms (Box 4)
  - Recipients Files
    - [A-Z] (Box 4)
  - Nominees (not approved) files
    - [A-H] (Box 4)
    - [I-Z] (Box 5)
  - Correspondence 1964-1967, undated, 4 folders (Box 5)
- Programs of University of Michigan schools, departments, colleges
  - General 1964-1967 (Box 5)
  - Committee Reports (Box 5)
  - Archaeology (Box 5)
  - Architecture and Design (Box 5)
  - Astronomy (Box 5)
  - Athletic Department (Box 5)
  - Business Administration (Box 5)
  - Classical Studies (Box 5)
  - Dearborn Center (Box 5)
  - Dentistry (Box 5)
  - Education (Box 5)
  - Engineering (Box 5)
  - English (Box 5)
  - Flint (Box 5)
  - Geology and Mineralogy (Box 5)
  - Graduate School (Box 5)
  - History (Box 5)
  - Institute for Social Research (Box 5)
  - Law School (Box 5)
  - Linguistics (Box 5)
  - Literature, Science and the Arts (Box 5)
  - Medical School (Box 5)
  - Music School (Box 5)
  - Natural Resources (Box 5)
  - Nursing (Box 5)
  - Pharmacy (Box 5)
  - Philosophy (Box 5)
  - Political Science (Box 5)
  - Psychology (Box 5)
  - Public Health (Box 5)
  - Social Work (Box 5)
  - Speech (Box 5)
- Invitations
  - Domestic Institutions [A-Z] (Box 5)
  - Foreign Institutions (Box 5)
  - Academies, Museums, Foundations (Box 5)
  - Card file of Invitation Responses (Box 6)
  - Rating Sheets [A-Z] (Box 6)
- Topical file
  - Alumnae Council 1965-1967 (Box 7)
  - Alumni Association undated, 1964-1967 (Box 7)
  - Ann Arbor Birthday Party 1967 (Box 7)
  - Ann Arbor Chamber of Commerce 1964-1967 (Box 7)
  - Ann Arbor City Commission 1964-1967 (Box 7)
  - Arthur Miller Festival 1965-1967 (Box 7)
  - Audio-Visual Material 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Budgetary Information 1966-1968 (Box 7)
  - Calendar and Scheduling 1964-1967 (Box 7)
  - Canadian-American Relations Conference 1966-1967 (Box 7)
  - Celebration of other Schools 1965-1967 (Box 7)
  - Ceremonials, Committee on 1963-1967 (Box 7)
  - Commemorative Postage Stamp 1959-1967 (Box 7)
  - Conferences on Campus 1964-1967 (Box 7)
  - Conferences on Campus 1964-1967 (cont.) (Box 8)
  - Congressional Breakfast 1967 (Box 8)
  - Congressional Relations 1965-1967 (Box 8)
  - Consulates 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Design Symbol, Commercial Application of 1965 (Box 8)
  - Embassies 1965-1967 (Box 8)
  - Exhibits 1965-1967 (Box 8)
  - Folk Festivals 1966 (Box 8)
  - Foreign Visitors 1965-1967 (Box 8)
  - Hackett, George 1962-1967 (Box 8)
  - Hatcher, Harlan 1963-1967 (Box 8)
  - Henderson (Aldo) Files (Box 8)
  - Henderson (Aldo) Files (cont.) (Box 9)
  - Honorary Degree Committee 1963-1967 (Box 9)
  - Housing 1966-1967 (Box 9)
  - International Center 1966 (Box 9)
  - International Congress of Orientalists 1964-1967 (Box 9)
  - Joiner, Charles 1963-1967 (Box 9)
  - License Plates 1963-1966 (Box 9)
  - Major Ceremonies Chairmen 1963-1964 (Box 9)
  - Monteith Dedication 1967 (Box 9)
  - Music Commissions 1964-1966 (Box 9)
  - Musical Productions 1964-1965 (Box 9)
  - Narrative History 1964-1965 (Box 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences 1965 (Box 9)
  - National Student Conference 1966 (Box 9)
  - Office of Education 1964-1966 (Box 9)
  - "Our Michigan" (publication) 1964-1966 (Box 9)
  - Painting 1964 (Box 9)
  - Panelists and Recorders 1966-1967 (Box 9)
  - Pictorial History 1963 (Box 9)
  - Postage Meters 1966 (Box 9)
  - Press and Magazines (Box 9)
  - Professional Theatre 1967 (Box 9)
  - Publications 1966-1967 (Box 10)
  - Research Volume 1965 (Box 10)
  - Senate Advisory Committee 1963-1966 (Box 10)
  - Sesquicentennial Award Medal 1967 (Box 10)
  - Sesquicentennial Information Desk 1966 (Box 10)
  - Smith, Allan
    - [Sesquicentennial Materials taken from Files of the Vice President for Academic Affairs] (Box 10)
  - Special Events (Box 10)
  - Speakers, Suggestions for 1963-1965 (Box 10)
  - Speeches (correspondence and drafts) 1963-1967 (Box 10)
  - State Commission 1967 (Box 11)
  - State Department 1964-1965 (Box 11)
  - State Participation 1964-1967 (Box 11)
  - Student Participation 1964 (Box 11)
  - Student Revue, "Out of Our Minds," 1966 (Box 11)
- Day File
  - Correspondence (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous
  - Includes drafts of programs, general correspondence, and clippings (Box 11)
- Audio-tapes of Major Ceremonies
  - Audio-tapes (Box 12)
- Photographs: Sesquicentennial events and office staff. Phil Davis Sesquicentennial Exhibition
  The major portion of this series contains negatives and contact prints of about 8000 photographs taken primarily by Phil Davis, professor of art at the University of Michigan. (Some of the photos were taken by Terry Sam, Gottfried Hogh, David Cornwell, and Guy Palazzola.)
  The photographs were taken in preparation for a 1967 exhibition, part of the University's sesquicentennial celebration. 264 photos were selected from the collection to be part of the exhibition, which was mounted outdoors on the wall between Hill Auditorium and the Michigan League. Later 141 photos selected from those exhibited were published as The University, published by the University of Michigan Press (call number FImu/E17/outsize).
  The exhibition photos were selected to follow the life of a University of Michigan student from registration to graduation, but the complete series documents a much broader range of university activities during the mid-1960s, including classroom, study, and leisure activities of students; faculty teaching and research; administrators and regents; buildings and other campus scenes; musical, theater, and athletic events; and off-campus activities such as research shops, Interlochen, Shady Trails Camp, and forestry and geology camps.
  The series is arranged by contact print sheet number. The contact sheets are 35mm prints unless otherwise noted. The entry for each contact sheet includes the contact sheet number, a description of the content/subject of the images, possibly a note on the size of film or camera used, and the number of frames on the sheet.
  A card index to subjects photographed is located with other photographic collection card indexes. (See the reference archivist for access to this index.) Appendix II to this inventory contains a list of the subject headings used in the card index.
  The copy of The University found in the Michigan Historical Collections printed collection (call number FImu/E17/outsize) has been annotated with the sheet number of each image used. For each photo used in the book, this series contains a number of other shots of the same subject.
  The Exhibition series also includes 1 folder of photos of Davis preparing his exhibition, 1 folder of views of the exhibition, and 1 folder listing the photos used in the exhibition with captions.
  - Captions (Box 13)
  - Photographs
    - Preparation of exhibition (Box 13)
    - Views of exhibition (Box 13)
    - Contact prints, photos taken for exhibition, 28 folders
      - Honors Convocation April 1965, 34 frames; 1 (Box 13)
      - Freshmen at orientation in East Quad, Mike Holmer, advisor, Mrs. Peace, Housemother (56mm), 10 frames; 2 (Box 13)
      - Street fair Tom Capi, SNCC, 36 frames; 3 (Box 13)
      - Art school. Drawing classes. End of Freshman orientation week, 28 frames; 4 (Box 13)
      - TV screen, launch of Gemini spacecraft. McDivitt and White (56mm), 10 frames; 5 (Box 13)
      - Airport reception, Willow Run (56mm), 12 frames; 5a (Box 13)
      - Astronauts. Motorcade and speeches. Also Convocation, 36 frames; 6 (Box 13)
      - (3 sheets) Convocation or commencement (56mm), 36 frames; 7 (Box 13)
      - Commencement 1965. Student in window studying. Architecture School., 29 frames; 8A (Box 13)
      - Commencement 1965. Stadium, 37 frames; 8B (Box 13)
      - Astronauts. Demonstration at Union. Palazzola in office. Diag shots. Studying. Outdoor recitation. Library checkout and reading room, 30 frames; 9 (Box 13)
      - Art faculty meeting. Prof. Paton addressing Business Administration luncheon [Campus scenes], 36 frames; 10 (Box 13)
      - Housing petition. Union. Studying, Diag. Running motorcycles, 22 frames; 11 (Box 13)
      - Moving traffic. Running cycles, 21 frames; 12 (Box 13)
      - Football Saturday-October 10, 1965. Rain and crowds, 36 frames; 13 (Box 13)
      - Campus (56mm), 12 frames; 14 (Box 13)
      - Campus (56mm), 12 frames; 15 (Box 13)
      - Law Library-carrels. Art student sketching Law Quad (56mm), 12 frames; 16 (Box 13)
      - Law library. Campus scenes (56mm), 12 frames; 17 (Box 13)
      - Naval ROTC review-long lens, 36 frames; 18 (Box 13)
      - Navy ROTC review. Also miscellaneous, 36 frames; 19 (Box 13)
      - Long lens. Campus and diag, 36 frames; 20 (Box 13)
      - Navy ROTC. Long lens, 16 frames; 21 (Box 13)
      - Navy ROTC. Sub-destroyer simulator, November 24, 28 frames; 22 (Box 13)
      - Negro kids in Science Museum (56mm), 12 frames; 23 (Box 13)
      - Law library-(56mm) 9, 24 (Box 13)
      - U-M Music student teachers at Dexter Grade School. Concert, 36 frames; 25 (Box 13)
      - Art students in Museum, 34 frames; 26 (Box 13)
      - Dr. Butsch. Mr. Ryman, Museum (56mm), 12 frames; 27 (Box 13)
      - Museum dioramist. Also 3 shots grad student, zoology, with pygmy owls (56mm), 12 frames; 28 (Box 13)
      - Registration-Nikon. Also Museum, Dr. Butsch in diorama, 36 frames; 29 (Box 13)
      - Registration-Nikon, 36 frames; 30 (Box 13)
      - Registration-Leika (2), 36 frames; 31 (Box 13)
      - Registration-Royal X Nikor, 35 frames; 32 (Box 13)
      - Heating-plant. Pharmacy grad researcher. [View in old library stacks], 36 frames; 33 (Box 13)
      - Botany class, microscopes. 2 shots in Pharmacy (56mm), 12 frames; 34 (Box 13)
      - Botany lecture and Laura Berkelay with plants, 35 frames; 35 (Box 13)
      - Dr. Wagner and botany lecture (56mm), 12 frames; 36 (Box 13)
      - Pharmacy. Mixing salves (56mm), 12 frames; 37 (Box 13)
      - Pharmacy. Chem library. Business Administration library, 36 frames; 38 (Box 13)
      - Lahti's and Cohen's design classes. Bus. Admins. Coffee Shop. [Botany Class], 36 frames; 39 (Box 13)
      - Negro kids in Museum. Dr. Tordhof with finches Museum (56mm), 12 frames; 40 (Box 13)
      - Union cafeteria. Lahti. Painting student. Faculty lounge, 36 frames; 41 (Box 13)
      - Faculty club pool, bridge, 34 frames; 42 (Box 13)
      - Faculty club pool. Business Administration coffee break, 36 frames; 43 (Box 13)
      - Business Administration coffee klatch, 36 frames; 44 (Box 13)
      - Art Gallery. Pottery studio, 35 frames; 45 (Box 13)
      - Flounders Club (swimming). [Cactus], 36 frames; 46 (Box 13)
      - Business Administration interviews in auditorium. McLaughlin and cactus (56rnm), 12 frames; 47 (Box 13)
      - McLaughlin, cactus. Glassblower, 24 frames; 48 (Box 13)
      - Glassblower. McLaughlin and cactus (56mm), 12 frames; 49 (Box 13)
      - Night shots of campus (56mm), 12 frames; 50 (Box 13)
      - Snails in tanks (56mm), 12 frames; 51 (Box 13)
      - Telephoto shots of walk and Haven Hall "fish bowl" (56nm), 12 frames; 52 (Box 13)
      - Winter Weekend signs. Econ building exterior. Diag (56mm), 12 frames; 53 (Box 13)
      - Signs on campus (56mm), 12 frames; 54 (Box 13)
      - Prof. Cowan, Business Administration, in office and classroom, 36 frames; 55 (Box 13)
      - Kelsey Museum, 36 frames; 56 (Box 13)
      - Fish collection in Museum (56mm), 10 frames; 57 (Box 13)
      - Business Administration classroom. Prof. Cowan. Projectionist, etc. Oberdick and students in box., 36 frames; 58 (Box 13)
      - Prof. Waldo Sweet, Latin. Prof. Kenneth Boulding, Economics. Dean Wm(?) Smith, Economics, 34 frames; 59 (Box 13)
      - Snail Collection: Vander Schalie et al. Girls dancing, Women's Athletic Building, 36 frames; 60 (Box 13)
      - Winter Weekend. Vaughn and Peace corps speech. Health Service records, 36 frames; 61 (Box 13)
      - Winter Weekend-21mm lens, 36 frames; 62 (Box 13)
      - Barbour Gym-Balance beam.; Weight lifters, 33 frames; 63 (Box 13)
      - Barbour Gym-Girls dance warmup. Lecture. Basketball., 36 frames; 64 (Box 13)
      - Barbour Gym-Wan(?) Weight lifter. Girls gymnastics., 33 frames; 65 (Box 13)
      - Winter Weekend. I.M. Building. Wines Field. Also Grad. meeting at Art School, 36 frames; 66 (Box 13)
      - UGLI night shots. Grad meeting at Art School., 36 frames; 67 (Box 13)
      - Health Service. Kid in bed. Mr. Barridge counseling., 36 frames; 68 (Box 13)
      - Campus buildings, 18 frames; 69 (Box 13)
      - Pershing Rifles drill team, Waterman Gym, 30 frames; 70 (Box 13)
      - Geology lab: Health Service (Psychiatric) Staff conference, 36 frames; 71 (Box 13)
      - Dentistry-Student-Instructor closeups, 35 frames; 72 (Box 13)
      - Dentistry-Pellix Ara(?), 30 frames; 73 (Box 13)
      - Dentistry-Children's Clinic (grainy film), 30 frames; 74 (Box 13)
      - Dentistry-Technic[ian] lab Children's Clinic. Old Bill, 35 frames; 75 (Box 13)
      - Forestry seminar. Old Bill. Dental teeth, 36 frames; 76 (Box 13)
      - Children's Dental Clinic. Student Shanklis(?). Chinese boy patient, 36 frames; 77 (Box 13)
      - Dentistry-Children's Clinic. Dr. Brown checking student work, 36 frames; 78 (Box 13)
      - Dentistry technician. Hands closeup, 36 frames; 79 (Box 13)
      - Clements Library.-Indian girl. Campus scenes. Regents Breakfast, 34 frames; 80 (Box 13)
      - Outdoor classes. Mrs. Vieterle., 36 frames; 81 (Box 13)
      - Students returning to Ann Arbor, Spring vacation. Depot, and Stockwell Hall, 32 frames; 82 (Box 13)
      - Herbarium (2), 36 frames; 83 (Box 13)
      - Regents Meeting-Tri X, 36 frames; 84 (Box 13)
      - Business Administration banquet and speech-2475, 36 frames; 85 (Box 13)
      - Regents meeting. Business Administration banquet. 2475, 36 frames; 86 (Box 13)
      - Business Administration conference and dinner-Tri X, 36 frames; 87 (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous, scraps, etc., 27 frames; 88 (Box 13)
      - Computer center punch room 2475, 36 frames; 89 (Box 13)
      - Indian girl directing TIV film in Clements Library. Business Administration conference, Rackham, 36 frames; 90 (Box 13)
      - Architecture student meeting-heads, 36 frames; 91 (Box 13)
      - Lou Briggs. Regents meeting (56mm), 12 frames; 92 (Box 13)
      - Architecture student meeting, general shots, 36 frames; 93 (Box 13)
      - Seales (geology) [geology storage in basement of plant department]. SGC voting. Architecture student meeting. Rain shots.[Charity collection.], 35 frames; 94 (Box 13)
      - Rain shots [SGC voting] Puppies. Business Administration conference, 36 frames; 95 (Box 13)
      - Fish bowl. Prof. Wilson with English student. Azozels Trix., 36 frames; 96 (Box 13)
      - Azozels. Long lens test, 36 frames; 97 (Box 13)
      - Azozels (At dinner table), 36 frames; 98 (Box 13)
      - Azozels dinner-Hobers. After dinner, 36 frames; 99 (Box 13)
      - Clements Library Founders Tea, 36 frames; 100 (Box 13)
      - Art grad orals. Technirama, 36 frames; 101 (Box 13)
      - Technirsunn.[Also Prof. Lewis, art], 36 frames; 102 (Box 13)
      - Ship model being glued up. Aldridge signing books, 36 frames; 103 (Box 13)
      - Aldridge signing books. Also class in horticulture-Inglis, 36 frames; 104 (Box 13)
      - Mr. Jenkins. Class in horticulture-Inglis, 36 frames; 105 (Box 13)
      - Maurer's seminar with Kersten Peager, 36 frames; 106 (Box 13)
      - Sculpture [class], 36 frames; 107 (Box 13)
      - Math Club, 36 frames; 108 (Box 13)
      - Language lab. Organ doctorate, 35 frames; 109 (Box 13)
      - Organ doctorate., 34 frames; 110 (Box 13)
      - Arboretum. Physics lab, 36 frames; 111 (Box 13)
      - Miss Kebbels landscape architecture class-arboretum and Inglis, 38 frames; 112 (Box 13)
      - Physiology classes, 36 frames; 113 (Box 13)
      - Percival Price [carilloneur, Burton Tower?]. Physiology class, 36 frames; 114 (Box 13)
      - Fencers in Waterman Gym. Sociology test. [Percival Price.] [Motorcycle repair] [no contact print], 37 frames; 115 (Box 13)
      - Music library. Drafting exam, 36 frames; 116 (Box 13)
      - Chorale-Hill Auditorium (from top). Botany exam. [Language lab], 36 frames; 117 (Box 13)
      - Drafting exam. Chet [LaMore?, art prof.]. Night campus. Ophthalmology lecture. [Music library.] [Outside South Quad.], 36 frames; 118 (Box 13)
      - Engineering stairway. Nuclear reactor tour, 30 frames; 129 (Box 13)
      - UGLI-Print study gallery and studying, 36 frames; 120 (Box 13)
      - A-B English Lit exam-W. Physics Auditorium, 121 (Box 13)
      - UGLI. Ulrich's book counter. [Outside Casa Dominick's restaurant]., 36 frames; 122 (Box 13)
      - Homegoing-Stockwell [and Alice Lloyd], 30 frames; 123 (Box 13)
      - Campus. UGLI doorways. (KB-14), 36 frames; 124 (Box 13)
      - Bookstores. Chemistry Building, 36 frames; 125 (Box 13)
      - Stockwell Hall [and Mosher-Jordan, Alice Lloyd]-going home (2). Underexposed panatomic X, 126 (Box 13)
      - [Stockwell Hall-going home. Glee Club rehearsal], 36 frames; 127 (Box 13)
      - Glee Club rehearsal, 38 frames; 128 (Box 13)
      - Commencement in Field House. Hausen and Overgardl(?) (56mm), 12 frames; 129 (Box 13)
      - Law Quad. Economics Building Commencement in Field House, 38 frames; 130 (Box 13)
      - Commencement in Field House. (56mm), 12 frames; 131 (Box 13)
      - Alumni Sing, Hill Auditorium (56mm), 12 frames; 132 (Box 13)
      - Ernie Jones conducts band (56mm), 12 frames; 133 (Box 13)
      - ROTC commissioning, Rackham. [Hill Auditorium], 30 frames; 134 (Box 13)
      - Baseball. Miscellaneous., 36 frames; 135 (Box 13)
      - 137 Rotating radar reflector, Willow Run (56mm), 25 frames; 136 (Box 13)
      - Sailboat on campus (56mm), 12 frames; 138 (Box 13)
      - Discus thrower. Pitcher. [Baseball game. Track], 38 frames; 139 (Box 13)
      - Commencement, Field House.(Guy's [Palazzola] negatives), 36 frames; 140 (Box 13)
      - Track meet (56mm), 12 frames; 141 (Box 13)
      - Track meet. Cazzie Russell Day, 36 frames; 142 (Box 13)
      - Cazzie Russell Day, 30 frames; 143 (Box 13)
      - Physics class, rotational motion. Diag scene, 36 frames; 144 (Box 13)
      - Bird hike, 28 frames; 145 (Box 13)
      - Daily editors lunch with vice president Pierpont, 36 frames; 146 (Box 13)
      - Chesaning Love Fest-remnants, 33 frames; 147 (Box 13)
      - Japanese student [at] Ray Turnward Farm, 36 frames; 148 (Box 13)
      - Chem lab, grad students, 36 frames; 149 (Box 13)
      - Campus-general candids (56mm), 12 frames; 150 (Box 13)
      - Drs. Votaw, et al-monkey surgery, 36 frames; 151 (Box 13)
      - Naval tank, 1st try, 34 frames; 152 (Box 13)
      - Lagler-anatomic, 14 frames; 153 (Box 13)
      - Lagler-Tri X, 35 frames; 154 (Box 13)
      - Naval tank-Lagler and grads on stream, 34 frames; 155 (Box 13)
      - Naval tank, 2nd try, 36 frames; 156 (Box 13)
      - Chemistry, 36 frames; 157 (Box 13)
      - Physics, Randall Lab, 36 frames; 158 (Box 13)
      - Bardack and fish trace (3 are 56mm), 26 frames; 159 (Box 13)
      - Bullheads-Pan X, 36 frames; 160 (Box 13)
      - Profile-Inland Seas with gulls and sun shoving. Tri X (56mm), 12 frames; 161 (Box 13)
      - Straight shots Tri X-Inlard Seas (56mm), 12 frames; 162 (Box 13)
      - Boats. [Inland Seas] Adox [?], 24 frames; 163 (Box 13)
      - Inland Seas head on and silhouette Plus X (56mm), 12 frames; 164 (Box 13)
      - Inland Seas-panatomic (56mm), 12 frames; 165 (Box 13)
      - Hospital, puppet show, 30 frames; 166 (Box 13)
      - Girls' orientation group at Health Service. Also hospital patio dedication, 22 frames; 167 (Box 13)
      - Sociology class. English class (King Lear). Boys' orientation group, 36 frames; 168 (Box 13)
      - English class-Lear., 36 frames; 169 (Box 13)
      - Language test, orientation. Med students studying X-ray film, 36 frames; 170 (Box 13)
      - Particle track recorders. Hospital surgical glove test. X-ray class, 36 frames; 171 (Box 13)
      - Sherman Kuhn-Middle English dictionary. Characters in Law Quad. Particle track recording, physics., 36 frames; 172 (Box 13)
      - Tree trimmer, 12 frames; 173 (Box 13)
      - Running cars, bikes, etc., 36 frames; 174 (Box 13)
      - " August "-Physics Machine Shop' (56mm), 12 frames; 175 (Box 13)
      - Physics Machine Shop, 28 frames; 176 (Box 13)
      - Forestry students in tree and moisture test. Middle English Dictionary editor, 36 frames; 177 (Box 13)